-...and I realize you're not even there.
-I know.
(Raj:)And where were you?
(Howard:)Getting shot down by the girl
at Hot Dog on a Stick.
But in my defense, she was gorgeous.
(Howard:)And working that squeezer
to make the lemonade...
(Howard:)...going up and down
and up and down....
(Howard:)It was like a free pole dance
right in the middle of the food court.
(Raj:)You're impossible.
(Howard:)Hey, at least I can talk to women
without being drunk.
(Raj:)Excuse me, I have selective mutism,
a recognized medical disorder.
(Raj:)You're just a douche.
(Howard:)No. You know what?
(Howard:)Maybe that's what this whole thing
is about.
(Howard:)You're not mad at me.
You're mad at yourself.
(Raj:)No, I'm mad at you.
I hate myself, but I'm mad at you.
Look, fine. You're mad at me. I get it.
Now--
(Howard:)How about we go
spend the day together?
(Howard:)Just the two of us.
We'll go anywhere you want.
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Raj:)Come on.